# Hoft Kenny

# FullStack web developer

Address: 5 Rotistraat, Commewijne

Birth:June 9, 2004

Phone:+597 853-4188

Google: hoftkenny@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kenny-hoft-1404051a9/

GitHub: https://github.com/Beefy-py

3+ years I've been in the web development field and now I'm seeking industry level experience to help companies or organizations manage and build better ones their applications while also improving my communication skills, problem solving and creativity.

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Technical**

- Javascript Very good
- ReactJS Good
- NodeJS Good
- Python Very good
- Django Fairly good

#### Languages

- Dutch- Very good
- Engels Good
- Spanish- Fairly good

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Tune Creative Studios (Apr 2022 - Nov 2022)

#### **Full-stack Developer**

- Donation website designed for flooding in the souths of Suriname: <a href="https://www.sadelo.org/">https://www.sadelo.org/</a>
- An admin dashboard website designed for processing payments. It has a darkmode function & can be signed in via JWT.https://payments-app.netlifv.app/
- Helped build a personal real estate website.
- An admin dashboard designed for the "Dalla" mobile app.

#### Bits Please Technologies (Dec 2022 - Present)

#### **Software Developer**

- Migrating the ReactJS version from the bitsplease website[https://www.bitsplease.org/] to NextJS
- Installing an ERP system on a VPS to manage day-to-day business activities more easily.

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### **Room Chat App React**

Designed with Socket.IO, React and NodeJS.

- Live Demo: [https://room-chat-app-mern.netlify.app/]
- Frontend Source Code: [https://github.com/Beefy-py/chat-app-client]
- Backend Source Code: [https://github.com/Beefy-py/chat-app-server]

#### **EDUCATION**

VWO-s SchoolsCommunityTamanredjo, Tamanredjo

October 2020 - 2023

#### **CERTIFICATES**

React Certificate, HackerRank

[https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/d30dcf753809]

### Javascript Mastery Part2 Certificate, CodeWithMosh

[https://codewithmosh.com/courses/310571/certificate]

## Python Certificate, HackerRank

[https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/ec14f8a51949]

Javascript Mastery Part1 Certificate, CodeWithMosh

[https://codewithmosh.com/courses/324741/certificate]